export const flashcardDatabase = [
  {
    id: "1",
    front:
      "According to our present theory of solar system formation, how did Earth end up with enough water to make oceans?",
    back: "The water was brought to the forming Earth by planetesimals that accreted beyond the orbit of Mars.",
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    front: "The 'giant impact hypothesis' refers to the idea that ",
    back: "our Moon formed when a Mars-size object collided with the young Earth. ",
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    front:
      "What do we mean when we say that a nucleus undergoes radioactive decay?",
    back: "-The number of protons or neutrons (or both) in the nucleus changes",
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    front:
      "According to present understanding, which of the following statements about the solar wind is not true?",
    back: "It is even stronger today than it was when the Sun was young. It was much stronger when the Sun was young. ",
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    front:
      "Which of the following best explains why we can rule out the idea that planets are usually formed by near-collisions between stars?",
    back: "Stellar near-collisions are far too rare to explain all the planets now known to orbit nearby stars. ",
  },
  {
    id: "6",
    front:
      "The nebular theory also predicts that the cloud will flatten into a disk as it shrinks in size. Which of the following best explains why the collapsing cloud should form a disk? ",
    back: "Colliding cloud particles exchange angular momentum and, on average, end up with the rotation pattern for the cloud as a whole.",
  },
  {
    id: "7",
    front:
      "According to our present theory of solar system formation, how did Earth end up with enough water to make oceans?",
    back: "The water was brought to the forming Earth by planetesimals that accreted beyond the orbit of Mars.",
  },
  {
    id: "8",
    front: "The 'giant impact hypothesis' refers to the idea that ",
    back: "our Moon formed when a Mars-size object collided with the young Earth. ",
  },
  {
    id: "9",
    front:
      "What do we mean when we say that a nucleus undergoes radioactive decay?",
    back: "-The number of protons or neutrons (or both) in the nucleus changes",
  },
  {
    id: "10",
    front:
      "According to present understanding, which of the following statements about the solar wind is not true?",
    back: "It is even stronger today than it was when the Sun was young. It was much stronger when the Sun was young. ",
  },
  {
    id: "11",
    front:
      "Which of the following best explains why we can rule out the idea that planets are usually formed by near-collisions between stars?",
    back: "Stellar near-collisions are far too rare to explain all the planets now known to orbit nearby stars. ",
  },
  {
    id: "12",
    front:
      "The nebular theory also predicts that the cloud will flatten into a disk as it shrinks in size. Which of the following best explains why the collapsing cloud should form a disk? ",
    back: "Colliding cloud particles exchange angular momentum and, on average, end up with the rotation pattern for the cloud as a whole.",
  },
  {
    id: "13",
    front:
      "According to our present theory of solar system formation, how did Earth end up with enough water to make oceans?",
    back: "The water was brought to the forming Earth by planetesimals that accreted beyond the orbit of Mars.",
  },
  {
    id: "14",
    front: "The 'giant impact hypothesis' refers to the idea that ",
    back: "our Moon formed when a Mars-size object collided with the young Earth. ",
  },
  {
    id: "15",
    front:
      "What do we mean when we say that a nucleus undergoes radioactive decay?",
    back: "-The number of protons or neutrons (or both) in the nucleus changes",
  },
  {
    id: "16",
    front:
      "According to present understanding, which of the following statements about the solar wind is not true?",
    back: "It is even stronger today than it was when the Sun was young. It was much stronger when the Sun was young. ",
  },
  {
    id: "17",
    front:
      "Which of the following best explains why we can rule out the idea that planets are usually formed by near-collisions between stars?",
    back: "Stellar near-collisions are far too rare to explain all the planets now known to orbit nearby stars. ",
  },
  {
    id: "18",
    front:
      "The nebular theory also predicts that the cloud will flatten into a disk as it shrinks in size. Which of the following best explains why the collapsing cloud should form a disk? ",
    back: "Colliding cloud particles exchange angular momentum and, on average, end up with the rotation pattern for the cloud as a whole.",
  },
];
